# Who!?

# Hossein Shouri,

# Front-end developer!



### **CONTACT**



(0098) 936 200 8656



Artshorey@gmail.com



Karaj, Alborz

### **SKILL**

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript/ECMAScript
- Bootstrap v4/v5
- React.js Basics
- o Git & GitHub Basics
- Basic knowledge on C, C# and Python
- Basic knowledge on Linux

## **INTERESTS**

- Programming
- o Tech
- Web Development
- Game Development
- Artificial Intelligence
- Digital Marketing

#### **HOBBIES**

- Boxing & Exercise
- Café Hoping
- Watching Sports

#### **EDUCATION**

 Computer Science Bachelor at IAUT west branch 2023 present

#### **PROFILE**

23 years old Computer Science student with a passion for programming and bringing new ideas to life through Coding! Always been fascinated with computers and working with them from early on. I'm always eager to learn and keeping myself up to date.

I've created some projects to show you I mean business on <u>GitHub</u>. Check out the <u>next page!</u>

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### O WEBSITE ADMINISTRATOR

Lmap institute Sep2021 - Apr2022

Posting and addressing day-to-day content on the website and social media platforms, designing posters and thumbnails for posts and editing day-to-day videos posted on the website's blog.

#### O MARKETING INTERN

Iran Social Media Apr2023 - Jun2023

I learnt basic marketing techniques such as copywriting, email marketing, social media some web design with wordpress.

#### O SEO CONTENT WRITER

Mohtavanet Nov2023 - Apr2024

Writing SEO optimized content for all kinds of websites using research and references.

#### **MY LINKS**









LinkedIn GitHub

Code Pen

Telegran

# **Hossein Shouri**



# **Projects**

#### O Roman numerals convertor

Converting Roman numbers to base-10 and vice versa

This was my first ever really challenging JavaScript project. I used bootstrap to quickly build a UI so I don't waste too much time on that. I came up with the algorithm by myself which was challenging at the time since it was the first algorithm I was coming up with all by myself. You can check out the code both on <u>GitHub</u> and <u>Code Pen</u>.

### O Guess my number

A little fun mini-game with numbers!

This is one of the mini-projects in Jonas Schmedtmann's "The Complete JavaScript Course", I didn't build the UI, Just the mechanics and game logic. This is also the first project I used git on. Check it out on <u>GitHub</u> or <u>Code Pen</u>.

# O Pig Game

Dice up and have fun!

Another one of Jonas Schmedtmann's "The Complete JavaScript Course" mini-projects, the UI is again not mine, I implemented the game logic and mechanics. I also kept up with program update's with git. Check it out on <u>GitHub</u> or <u>Code Pen</u> right now!